[
    {
        "qid": 673249,
        "question": "Patient is a 9 year old female.<br>- The patient regularly takes stimulant drugs.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has felt like they were suffocating for a very short time, associated with an inability to breathe or speak.<br>- The patient has been treated in hospital recently for nausea, agitation, intoxication, or aggressive behavior and received medication via an intravenous or intramuscular route.<br>- The patient has trouble keeping their tongue in their mouth.<br>- The patient is unable to control the direction of their eyes.<br>- The patient feels that muscle spasms or soreness in their neck are keeping them from turning their head to one side.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient suddenly has difficulty or an inability to open their mouth or experiences jaw pain when opening it.",
        "option1": "Acute COPD exacerbation / infection",
        "option2": "Laryngospasm",
        "option3": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option4": "Acute otitis media",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "87%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 267119,
        "question": "Patient is a 41 year old female.<br>- The patient has started or taken antipsychotic medication within the last 7 days.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has trouble keeping their tongue in their mouth.<br>- The patient has a hard time opening or raising one or both eyelids.<br>- The patient is unable to control the direction of their eyes.<br>- The patient feels that muscle spasms or soreness in their neck are keeping them from turning their head to one side.<br>- The patient has annoying muscle spasms in their face, neck, or another part of their body.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Pneumonia",
        "option2": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option3": "Acute COPD exacerbation / infection",
        "option4": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "73%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 993458,
        "question": "Patient is a 9 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest and the posterior chest wall on the right side.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a cough that produces colored or more abundant sputum than usual.<br>- The patient has chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD).<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has noticed a wheezing sound when they exhale.",
        "option1": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option2": "Allergic sinusitis",
        "option3": "Influenza",
        "option4": "Bronchitis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "57%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 538334,
        "question": "Patient is a 43 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain on the right side of the chest, the left side of the chest, and the upper chest.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is located with a precision of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a cough that produces colored or more abundant sputum than usual.<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has noticed a wheezing sound when they exhale.",
        "option1": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option2": "Pulmonary embolism",
        "option3": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option4": "Bronchitis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "76%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 1009353,
        "question": "Patient is a 4 year old male.<br>- The patient has recently had a viral infection.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain on the left side of the chest.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has noticed new fatigue, generalized and vague discomfort, diffuse muscle aches, or a change in their general well-being related to their consultation today.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's symptoms are worse when lying down and alleviated while sitting up.",
        "option1": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option2": "Myasthenia gravis",
        "option3": "Myocarditis",
        "option4": "Systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE)",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "93%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 788539,
        "question": "Patient is a 76 year old female.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient is significantly overweight compared to people of the same height as them.<br>- The patient drinks alcohol excessively or has an addiction to alcohol.<br>- The patient has a hiatal hernia.<br>- The patient thinks they are pregnant or are currently pregnant.<br>- The patient has a burning sensation that starts in their stomach, goes up into their throat, and can be associated with a bitter taste in their mouth.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's symptoms are worse when lying down and alleviated while sitting up.",
        "option1": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "option2": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option3": "Acute pulmonary edema",
        "option4": "Bronchitis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "68%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 800573,
        "question": "Patient is a 35 year old female.<br>- The patient attends or works in a daycare.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the thyroid cartilage, palate, pharynx, and under the jaw.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is located with a precision of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has noticed that the tone of their voice has become deeper, softer, or hoarse.",
        "option1": "Acute laryngitis",
        "option2": "Anemia",
        "option3": "Myasthenia gravis",
        "option4": "Pericarditis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "68%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 888505,
        "question": "Patient is a 0 year old male.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient attends or works in a daycare.<br>- The patient has had significantly increased sweating.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has diffuse (widespread) muscle pain.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient is exposed to secondhand cigarette smoke on a daily basis.",
        "option1": "Acute COPD exacerbation / infection",
        "option2": "Boerhaave",
        "option3": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option4": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "67%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 590872,
        "question": "Patient is a 41 year old female.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient attends or works in a daycare.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right tonsil, thyroid cartilage, palate, pharynx, and under the jaw.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10) for the patient.<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has noticed that the tone of their voice has become deeper, softer, or hoarse.",
        "option1": "Guillain-Barr√© syndrome",
        "option2": "Bronchospasm / acute asthma exacerbation",
        "option3": "Anemia",
        "option4": "Acute laryngitis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "73%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 315646,
        "question": "Patient is a 71 year old male.<br>- The patient has been in contact with a person with similar symptoms in the past 2 weeks.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right tonsil, thyroid cartilage, palate, and under the jaw.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option2": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option3": "Pneumonia",
        "option4": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "44%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 638821,
        "question": "Patient is a 29 year old female.<br>- The patient feels anxious.<br>- The patient regularly drinks coffee or tea.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient consumes energy drinks regularly.<br>- The patient regularly takes stimulant drugs.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast (racing), irregularly (missing a beat), or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has recently taken decongestants or other substances that may have stimulant effects.",
        "option1": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option2": "Epiglottitis",
        "option3": "Boerhaave",
        "option4": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "68%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 907238,
        "question": "Patient is a 13 year old female.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the left tonsil, thyroid cartilage, palate, pharynx, and trachea.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has noticed that the tone of their voice has become deeper, softer, or hoarse.",
        "option1": "Bronchitis",
        "option2": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option3": "Allergic sinusitis",
        "option4": "Acute laryngitis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "62%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 1049152,
        "question": "Patient is a 36 year old male.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is tedious.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right cheek, left cheek, and left temple.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has diffuse (widespread) muscle pain.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient is exposed to secondhand cigarette smoke on a daily basis.",
        "option1": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option2": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option3": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option4": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "77%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 850052,
        "question": "Patient is a 62 year old male.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right tonsil, left tonsil, pharynx, and trachea.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10) for the patient.<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has noticed that the tone of their voice has become deeper, softer, or hoarse.",
        "option1": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option2": "Acute laryngitis",
        "option3": "Pulmonary neoplasm",
        "option4": "Bronchospasm / acute asthma exacerbation",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "46%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 1145370,
        "question": "Patient is a 11 year old male.<br>- The patient regularly takes stimulant drugs.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has felt like they were suffocating for a very short time, associated with an inability to breathe or speak.<br>- The patient has been treated in the hospital recently for nausea, agitation, intoxication, or aggressive behavior and received medication via an intravenous or intramuscular route.<br>- The patient has trouble keeping their tongue in their mouth.<br>- The patient has a hard time opening or raising one or both eyelids.<br>- The patient is unable to control the direction of their eyes.<br>- The patient feels that muscle spasms or soreness in their neck are keeping them from turning their head to one side.<br>- The patient has annoying muscle spasms in their face, neck, or another part of their body.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient suddenly has difficulty or an inability to open their mouth or experiences jaw pain when opening it.",
        "option1": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option2": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option3": "Laryngospasm",
        "option4": "Pericarditis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "86%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    }
]